

SKILLS

- -Project Management Software
- -Microsoft Office Suite
- -HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python
- -Working knowledge of AI
- -Schedule Management Software
- -Accounting Software
- -Grant writing for 501c3 organizations
- -ERP programs (SAP)
- -Transcription technology
- -Translation (Spanish & Chinese)

PROFILE

Experienced manager in both for-profit and nonprofit sectors with a history teaching in alternative spaces. Formal education in project management and writing, currently learning computer programming for possible web development and effective technical project management roles. Former resident of China. Best cultural fit is a workplace that offers a balance of guidance and autonomy for optimal performance.

CONTACT

PHONE: 304-543-9906

WEBSITE:

JonnyBlevins.Codes

linkedin.com/in/ionnvblevins/

EMAIL:

blevinsjonny@gmail.com

JONNY BLEVINS

Solid communication with fundamental technical knowledge

WORK EXPERIENCE

Shepherd Communication & Security, Project Manager

June 2022 - February 2023

Managed 50+ projects with varying scopes (6-400 hours), using a custom PM program called Promys. Drove communication, education, data management, performance, and reporting. Reported business optimization ideas and quality control, growing the business by \$1 million annually.

Northern Clearing, Inc, Project Manager

Nov 2020 - June 2022

Created timely, accurate reports with Excel and Adobe programs in a fast-paced field labor project contracted for \$300,000 per month. Built strategic relationships with subcontractors and vendors to ensure project milestones were met above expectation, particularly during the covid-19 pandemic and the Suez Canal obstruction. Resolved business issues with RFIs, analyzed and tracked key metrics, and produced meticulous cost reports.

Cox Well Services, LLC, Tech Specialist | Assistant Business Manager May 2020 – Nov 2020

Submitted effective bids by interpreting historical project information, created website and visual materials for improved optics, all managed through Quickbooks and SAP landing \$200,000 of summer bids.

IMPACT Communities, Property Manager

October 2019 - May 2020

Maintained 0% delinquency of approximately 100 units through RentManager software, and raised existing site gross revenue by \$13,000.

TC Energy, Material Coordinator | Admin | Field Planner

February 2017 - January 2019

Ensured that materials, paperwork, and records were accurate and met TC Energy specifications. Worked with Excel, Oracle's Primavera P6, and Microsoft Project programs for \$24 billion in U.S. Major Projects.

EDUCATION

AlbanyCanCode - Front End Web Development

June 2023 (In progress)

Job Training for FEWD including HTML, CSS, and Javascript.

University of Pittsburgh - Joseph M. Katz School of Business

January 2016 - May 2017

Master's Certificate in Project Management

Chatham University

August 2013 - May 2015

Master of Fine Arts in Creative Nonfiction / Professional Writing Focus Mansell-Reich Fellowship; Taught 6 semesters of writing courses

West Virginia University

August 2006 – December 2010

Bachelor of Fine Arts in English Literature / Spanish Literature